cut-mp3.com 2018-10-31

# Privacy Policy

## General provisions

This Privacy Policy governs the collection, use and storage of information (hereinafter: Information) and any data (hereinafter: Data) obtained through your use of our 123apps website available at[123apps.com](https://123apps.com/) and websites provided by 123apps LLC available at following urls:[pdf.io](https://pdf.io/),[mp3cut.net](https://mp3cut.net/),[audio-cutter.com](https://audio-cutter.com/),[online-audio-converter.com](https://online-audio-converter.com/),[audio-joiner.com](https://audio-joiner.com/),[convert-video-online.com](https://convert-video-online.com/),[online-video-cutter.com](https://online-video-cutter.com/),[online-voice-recorder.com](https://online-voice-recorder.com/),[webcamera.io](https://webcamera.io/) and[extract.me](https://extract.me/)(all collectively called: Sites) and any service available on the Sites (hereinafter: Services). We do not sell, rent or otherwise make available Information or Data to third-parties. We use collected Information and Data for our internal purposes and as necessary by the nature of the Services. In some instances, we are obliged to comply with court orders and government requests and provide Information or parts of it to authorized bodies. We may disclose or access Information whenever we believe in good faith that the law so requires, such as to comply with a litigation, or that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or if we otherwise consider it necessary to do so to maintain service and improve our products and services. The Information on users is divided into personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable Information depending on whether Information can identify the user as a specific person. 

This policy is effective from 18 November 2017.

## Changes to the Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy at any time without prior notification. The current version of Privacy Policy is available on the Site, indicating the effective date. You are encouraged to periodically check our Privacy Policy.

## Consent

By accessing the Sites you agree to have your Information and Data handled as described in this Privacy Policy. The services are intended for a general audience and are not targeted at children.

## Personally identifiable information

No registration is necessary for the use of our Services. We do not collect any personally identifiable information, your IP address, or any other Information which either alone or in connection with other data can be used to identify you.

If you send an e-mail to our e-mail address indicated on the Sites, we may keep records of such communication and any question, complaint or compliment made by you and the response if any. Whenever you contact us, we will only use your e-mail address in order to provide the response, if any. We do not store your e-mail address nor use it for any other purpose.

We endeavor to maintain appropriate physical, procedural and technical security with respect to the collected information so as to prevent any loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, or modification of personal information which also applies to our disposal or destruction of personal information. Our Sites uses SSL encryption in order to provide additional security of your information.

## Non-personally identifiable information and data

During your use of our Service, you may provide us with Non-Personally Identifiable Information and Data as necessary by the nature of the Service. You can either upload Data on your own or use Cloud Providers (Google Drive or Dropbox) to upload your Data from cloud storage.

We use such Information and Data only for the purpose of providing you with the Service requested and to improve the user experience. We do not monitor or access the Data provided by you. Processing of the Information and Data is completely automated without any human interaction or supervision.

If you choose to upload your Data through the Cloud Providers, you are giving us permission to access and to view, download and interact with such Data. We are only interacting with the Data in a way that is strictly necessary by the nature of the requested Service. We do not access, collect, use or store any Data or Information that is not necessary to provide you with the Service requested.

Any Data which you provide for the purpose of utilizing our Services is stored on our servers only for as long as necessary, and is deleted automatically no later than twelve (12) hours from the moment you complete your use of our Services.

## Cookies and similar technologies

Cookies help us optimize and improve the user experience of the Sites by helping us deliver crucial functionalities. The cookies we use may vary over time as we continuously update and improve our Sites. Use of cookies is further explained in article 8 of this Privacy Policy.

By visiting the Sites we may use cookies to store some non-identifiable Information in your browser regarding your computer or mobile device and your activities in order to help improve the User experience. Users can deny access to cookies through their browser settings.

## Third party websites, services, and cookies

The Sites may contain links to other external websites that do not fall under our domain. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such external websites. If you choose to follow such links to external websites, you do so at your risk.

We may use third party services like Google Analytics and AdSense. Cookies from such services are used to collect data for statistical reports and to provide ads.

Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to the Sites. Any data collected will be used in accordance with our Privacy Policy and Google’s privacy policy. Users may opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting the Google Advertising Opt-out Page, also, Users may opt out of Google Analytics by visiting the Google Analytics Opt-out Page. Users may opt out of third-party vendor use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative Opt-out Page.

## Use of your information

We use your information in order to deliver our Services, to analyze the use of the Sites, and the Services, to develop new products or services, optimize content, to provide support and to deliver ads based on your preferences. Processing of the Information and Data is automated and done without any supervision or interference by the physical person.

Your information is processed and handled in accordance with applicable laws and with your further consent where necessary.

Third party service providers may use your information for ads placement and notifications. We do not encourage, support or endorse any ad that is placed on the Sites. We have provided you with the full list of third-party services we are using in order to help you understand how your information is handled and you are encouraged to visit their respective privacy policies in order to exercise your right to the control of your personal information.

## Contact information

If you have any questions regarding our Privacy Policy and how the information is handled, or you wish to access, amend, or update your information feel free to contact us at [m@123apps.com](mailto:m@123apps.com).
